DVD2AVI : 한승[H2S]
SUB2SMI : Eugene
리치몬드 연애 소동
1 9 8 2
See the people
walking down the street
Fall in line
just watching all their feet
They don't know
where they want to go
But they're walking in time
숀 펜 (제프 役)
They got the beat
They got the beat, yeah
제니퍼 제이슨 리 (스테이시 役)
저지 레인홀드 (브레드 해밀톤 役)
피비 케이츠 (린다 바렛 役)
All the kids
just gettin' out of school
브라이언 베커 (마크 役)
They can't wait
to hang out and be cool
Hang around 'til quarter after 12:00
That's when they fall in line
로버트 로마누스 (마이크 다몬 役)
They got the beat
Kids got the beat, yeah
Kids got the beat
Go-go music
really makes us dance
Do the Pony
puts us in a trance
Do the Watusi, just give us a chance
That's when we fall in line
'Cause we got the beat
We got the beat
We got the beat, yeah
We got it
We got the beat
Everybody, get on your feet
We know you can dance to the beat
We got the beat
Jump back, get down
'Round and 'round and 'round
We got the beat
린다, 쟤가 오디오 전문점에서
일하는 남자애야
Linda, there's that guy
from the stereo store.
- Don't you think
he looks like Richard Gere?
- See his cute little butt?
꼭 리차드 기어 같지 않니?
섹시하지 않니?
얘들아, 여기 막 들어온
저 킹카 얘기 하자
- You guys, let's talk about
that fox that just walked in.
- We already were.
벌써 하는 중이야
I'm gonna go over there
and change the shakers.
가서 인사하고 올게
진정해, 스테이시 관할이야
- Cool out. That's Stacy's section.
- He's too old.
나이가 너무 많잖아
She's not even
in high school yet.
쟨 아직 고등학교도
졸업 안했어
Smoking's upstairs to your left.
흡연석은 윗층 왼쪽입니다
흡연석은 윗층 왼쪽에 있습니다
Smoking's upstairs to your left.
Smoking's upstairs.
마이크, 여기서 열심히 일하면
예쁜 여자라도 꼬이냐?
Rat, is Dolly Parton giving you
a percentage of the profit?
What can I do for you, gentlemen?
뭘 도와줄까?
밴 할렌 콘서트 티켓
파는 사람이죠?
You the guy with
the Van Halen tickets?
That could be.
그럴수도 있지
맨 앞자리 구하려면
얼마예요?
How much for something
in the first ten rows?
한사람에 20달러야
- Twenty bucks apiece.
- Those tickets were only $12.50.
원래 12달러 50센트잖아요
So don't buy 'em.
그럼 사지 마
다른 암표상들도
다 매진이래
All the other scalpers are sold out.
Scalper?
Did you call me a scalper?
암표상?
날 암표상이라고 불렀냐?
Listen, gentlemen, I perform a service
here, and the service costs money.
이봐, 잘들어, 난 여기서 봉사를
하고 그 댓가를 받는거야
티켓 줘 말어?
Do you want the tickets or don't you?
좋아요, 살게요
Okay, we'll take 'em.
All right.
What'd I say, $25?
좋아, 25달러였었지?
20달러요!
Twenty!
좋아
All right.
Thank you.
고맙다
바로 16달러 벌었다
Just made 16 bucks, Rat.
What's the matter? You look depressed.
왜 그래?
우울해 보이네
극장에서 일하는거 정말 짜증나
예쁜 여잔 전부 반대편에 있잖아
I hate working the theater. All the
action's on the other side of the mall.
- How's it going?
- You want to take his table?
- 잘 돼가?
- 네가 대신 가볼래?
Go for it.
He's cute.
남자 괜찮던데
잘해봐
Just take his order,
look him in the eye.
그냥 주문을 받고
눈을 쳐다 봐
농담을 하면 정말
재미있는듯이 웃어주면 돼
If he says anything remotely funny,
laugh like you never heard anything
so funny.
And smile!
미소짓고!
Go for it.
잘해봐
So, you working hard or hardly working?
일을 열심히 하나
간신히 하나?
You look like you
could still be in high school.
고등학생처럼 보이네
I know.
Everybody says that.
알어요, 전부 그렇게 말들 하죠
몇살이야?
- How old are you?
- Nineteen.
19살, 그쪽은요?
- How old are you?
- Twenty-six.
26살
Do you think we could
still be friends?
친구 할 수 있겠지?
So what can I get you?
뭐 갖다 줄까요?
미트볼 샌드위치랑
How 'bout a meatball sandwich,
콜라 하나랑...
a medium Coke,
and your phone number?
네 전화번호!
- Hi.
- Hello.
저리 가, 브래드
Get outta here, Bradley.
- 데이브
- 왔어?
- Dave.
- How you doin', Brad?
벌써 요리중이야!
Cookin'!
Daddy's home, boys.
내가 왔단다, 얘들아
감자튀김은 싱싱하게
제공을 해야지
I shall serve no fries
before their time.
네가 살 차례야
This one's on you, dude.
Who's got the beaucoup dolares today?
오늘 누가 돈이 있냐?
Uno dinero.
1달러 있어
넌 얼마나 있어?
- What have you got, Mr. Buck Man?
- I got a cigarette.
담배는 있다
난 10센트 있다
I got uno "nickelette."
이봐! 여기 올때는
옷을 입고 들어와
Hey! You guys had shirts on
when you came in here.
오늘 황당한 일이 있었어
Somethin' happened to 'em, man.
그러지 마, 스피콜리
빨리 옷 입어
Come on, Spicoli,
just put the shirts back on.
You see that sign?
저기 표지판 보여?
옷 안 입고, 신발 안 신으면...
"No shirts. No shoes. No dice."
출입금지
Right.
맞아
배우고 알았으면
똑바로 행동해
Learn it.
Know it. Live it.
와
- Whoa.
- He's the full hot orator.
끝내주는 웅변가야
린다, 내가 이거 보여줬니?
그 오빠가 명함 줬다
Linda, did I show you this?
He gave me his card.
론 존슨, 오디오 전문 상담가
"Ron Johnson, Audio Consultant."
액자 해서 벽에 걸어야겠네
Maybe we should get a frame for this,
and put it up on the wall.
백화점에서 남자친구 사귈거라고
말했던건 너야
Linda, you're the one who told me
I was gonna get a boyfriend at the mall.
이번 주 안에 전화가 올까?
- Do you think he'll call this week?
- Why don't you call him?
네가 먼저 해
못해
- I can't.
- You can. Guys love that sort of thing.
할 수 있어!
남자들은 그런 거 좋아해
정말?
- Really?
- Yes!
그럼!
스테이시, 얼마나 더 기다리려고?
너 벌써 15살이야
Stacy, what are you waiting for?
You're 15 years old.
난 13살에 첫경험 했어
대단한게 아니라 겨우 섹스야
I did it when I was 13.
It's no huge thing. It's just sex.
그 오빠 괜찮았지?
- He was hot, wasn't he?
- If I didn't have a fiance
in Chicago, I'd go for it.
내 애인이 시카고에 없다면
내가 낚아챘을거다
Hey, how you doin'?
Welcome to Ridgemont.
난 게이다
Will it look okay?
Well, she was an American girl
Raised on promises
혹시 F10 번이 어디 있는지 알어?
- Do you know where U.S. History is?
- Down the hall and turn left.
복도 끝까지 가서
왼쪽으로 가봐
Somewhere else
She was an American girl
Hi, Bradley.
안녕, 브래들리
많이 컸네
보기 좋아
Grown up.
Lookin' good.
일년 지나니 결국
키스까지 하는군
Another year joined at the lips.
- Hi, Brad!
- Denise. I'd make you see God.
안녕, 브래드!
드니스, 내가 킹카임을 보여주지
Brad!
차 환상인데!
- Big Cruising Vessel!
- Bradley!
고마워
Thank you.
Six more payments, gentlemen,
and this beautiful...
6개월만 할부를 더 부으면
이 파랗고 멋진 세단이
아주 내 차가 되지!
blue, four-door, luxury sedan
is all mine!
I'll give you
four tickets in the fifth row...
다섯번째 줄 티켓 네장을
for the low price of $140.
아주 저렴한 가격인
저 차 보여?
See that car? Some alumni
gave Jefferson that car...
어느 졸업생이 제퍼슨이 2학년때
미식축구를 한다고 선물했지
for playing football
when he was a sophomore.
내가 받도록 도와줬지
- Helped him pick it out.
- Slick car.
차 끝내준다
우린 오래된 친구사이야
We go way back, you know.
Hey, Charles, how you doin', buddy?
Car looks great. I mean really terrific.
찰스, 잘 지냈어?
차 좋아보이네
내 말은 차 정말 멋져
관리를 정말 잘했구나
You're really keeping it up
wonderfully.
얼씬도 하지 마!
Don't fuck with it!
이런! 내 친구들이
좀 터프 해
Shit!
That's my man.
Brad?
- Arnold! What's happening?
- Can I talk to you a minute?
아놀드! 잘 지냈어?
잠깐 얘기 좀 할 수 있어?
Sure, man.
그래
I really hate Bronco Burger.
난 정말 브론코
햄버거 숍이 싫걸랑
치킨 너겟을 팔기 시작한 이후론
맨날 적자가 나기 시작했어
Ever since they started with the chicken
nuggets, everything went downhill.
You have to fry all their greasy food,
and you have to polish things.
기름기 줄줄 흐르는 음식을 튀겨서
나중에 다시 치장을 하지
And the manager's an asshole.
I was just wondering...
매니저는 정말 못됐고
그래서 생각중인데...
아놀드, 올 아메리칸 버거숍에서
일하고 싶다는 거니?
Arnold, do you want to work
at All-American Burger?
Yeah, well, um...
응, 그러니깐...
아마 일하게 해줄수 있을거야
우리 매니저한테 물어볼게
I can probably get you in.
Just let me talk to Dennis Taylor.
- All right!
- Okay.
- 좋았어!
- 알았어
Wait.
Did you hear the bell ring?
잠깐, 종 쳤냐?
- 무슨 종?
- 우린 벌써 왔잖아
- What bell?
- We're here.
Aloha.
알로하
내 이름은 미스터 핸드입니다
My name is Mr. Hand.
I have but one question for you.
질문은 단지 하나
Can you attend my class?
내 수업을
빠지지 않을수 있나요?
It is for your own good. And if you
can't make it, I can make you.
제군들을 위한 것이고
만약 못하겠다면
내가 그렇게 하도록 만들어 주죠
We have a 20-question quiz every Friday.
매주 금요일엔 20문제씩
쪽지 시험이 있고
성적은 모든 쪽지 시험의
평균들과 중간고사와
Your grade is the average
of all your quizzes,
전체의 3분의 1을 차지할
기말고사의 합계로 계산 합니다
plus the midterm and final
which counts for one-third.
이해 되요?
Got it?
또한...
Also...
수업시간에 음식은
먹을수 없어요, 절대로...
There will be no eating. E
-A
-T-l
-N
-G.
수업시간에 음식은
안돼요!
No eating in this class!
개인적인 일은 개인적인 시간에
알아서들 하도록 하세요
You get used to doing
your own business on your own time.
이게 내가 요구하는
한가지 사항입니다
That's one demand I make.
Just like you wouldn't want me
to come to your house...
내가 자네 집에 어느날
저녁 찾아가서
미국역사를 논하자고 하길
원하진 않겠죠?
- and discuss U.S. History
on your time, understand?
- Yes, sir.
네
This guy's been stoned
since the third grade.
쟤는 초등학교 3학년때부터
맛이 갔었어
- 무슨 일이죠?
- 이 반에 등록 됐는데요
- Yes?
- Yeah, I'm registered in this class.
- What class?
- This is U.S. History.
무슨 반이요?
여기 미국 역사반 이잖아요
저기 지구본도 보이네요
- I see the globe right there.
- Really?
그래요?
Hey.
May I come in?
- 들어가도 돼요?
- 들어와요!
Oh, please!
3교시 종이 울릴 때
내 학생들이 전부 안오면
I get so lonely when I hear
that third attendance bell ring...
나도 참 외로워 지죠
and all my kids are not here.
늦어서 죄송해요, 그러니깐
새 시간표가 너무 헷갈려서요
Sorry, I'm late. It's just like
this new schedule's totally confusing.
I know that dude!
저 쟤 알아요!
Mr. Spicoli.
스피콜리군
부모님이 지어준 이름이죠
That's the name they gave me.
- 시간표를 찢었잖아요!
- 그랬죠
- You're ripping my card!
- Yes.
뭐가 문제야?
Hey, bud, what's your problem?
아무 문제 없다네
No problem at all.
교무실이 어딘지는
알거라고 믿어요
I think you know
where the front office is.
You dick!
나쁜 자식!
I have taken the time
to print up a complete schedule...
이 반의 쪽지 시험과
진도 과정을 적은
이 반의 일정표를
준비해 왔습니다
of class quizzes
and the chapters they cover.
뒷사람에게 전달하세요
Please pass them
to the desk behind you.
Back, back, back.
뒤로...
Did you hear about this surfer guy
who pulled a knife on Mr. Hand
this morning?
오늘 아침에 제프가 핸드선생님에게
칼을 들이댄 얘기 들었어?
Oh, no!
He just called him a dick.
아냐!
그냥 나쁜 자식이라고만 말했어
A dick? Oh, God.
People exaggerate so much here.
나쁜 자식? 말도 안돼
정말 엄청들 불려서 소문 낸다니깐
Linda, that girl
looks just like Pat Benatar.
린다, 지금 지나간 여자 얘
가수 팻 베네터 닮지 않았니?
I know. Wait.
There are three girls at Ridgemont...
그러게, 잠깐
리치몬드에 그 가수 닮은
여자가 3명 있어
who have cultivated
the Pat Benatar look.
Chanel Semlar,
샤넬 셈라랑
Mary Ann Zlotnick
in the red tights.
빨간 타이즈를 입은
마리 즐토닉이랑...
Do you think guys find that
more attractive?
남자들이 저런걸
더 매력있어 하나?
Stacy, please, give me a break!
You are so much prettier!
말도 안 되는 소리 하지 마
쟤들보단 네가 훨씬 더 예뻐
Yeah, I know, but do you think
they'd be better in bed?
그건 알지만 저런 얘들이
잠자리는 더 끝내줄까?
What do you mean?
You either do it or you don't.
무슨 소리야?
그건 하고 안하고 둘밖에 없어
No. There are like... variables
that I might not be good at.
아니, 내가 잘 못하는 것을
더 다양하게 잘할수도 있잖아
무슨 다양함?
- Like what variables?
- Like, you know, giving blow jobs.
그러니깐...
입으로 해주는거
What's the big deal?
그게 뭐 대단해?
한번도 안 해봤어
- I never did it.
- You've never given a blow job?
정말 입으로
한번도 안 해봤어?
한번도? 별거 아니야
정말 쉬워
Never? Stace, there's nothing to it.
It's so easy.
Check it out.
야! 저기 봐!
Relax your throat muscles.
목 근육에 긴장 풀어
Don't bite.
물진 마
그리곤 밀어 넣어
And slide it in.
Try it again.
다시 해봐
Good. Push it slowly in and out.
You got it.
좋아, 천천히 넣었다 빼
바로 그거야
Okay.
알았어
하나만 물어봐도 돼?
절대 웃지 마!
- Can I ask you something
and you promise not to laugh?
- Sure.
알았어
Okay. When a guy has an orgasm,
how much comes out?
남자가 절정에 가면
얼마나 많이 나와?
A quart or so.
한 1리터 정도
No, I'm just kidding.
농담이야
연습 계속 해
Just practice.
난 시체실에 안갈거야
엄마한테 메모 써달라고 할거야
I'm not going to a morgue.
I'll get my mom to write a note.
Nobody's getting me into a room
with a bunch of dead guys.
죽은 시체들이 득실거리는 방에
가라곤 아무도 강요 못해
You have to go.
I hear it's part of the final.
기말고사의 일부라
가야만 해
정말 구역질 난다고 들었는데
왜들 가는지 알아?
I hear it's really disgusting.
Do you know what they do?
- 들었어?
- 뭘?
- Have you heard?
- What?
시체를 해부하고
The bodies are dissected
and Mr. Vargas...
바가스 선생님이 장기들을 꺼내서
들고 보여준대
pulls out parts of the dead body
and holds them up.
손을 넣고 내장들을
꺼낸단 말이야?
You mean, he reaches in
and pulls this stuff out?
위장이나 종양 같은거?
- Like stomach and tumors or something?
- Yeah, stomach, tumors, entrails.
그래, 위장이랑 종양이랑
창자들 말이야
Good day, everyone.
My name is Mr. Vargas.
모두 안녕
난 바가스 선생님이란다
Look.
I'm a little slow today.
오늘 내가 좀 둔할거야
커피를 다른 상표로 바꿔서 그러니
좀 봐주길 바란다
I just switched to Sanka,
so have a heart.
All right, now.
좋아, 그럼
'삶의 세계' 이게 우리가 사용할
교과서의 이름이란다
The World of Life. That is the name
of the textbook we will be using.
I'm in love.
나 사랑에 빠졌어
See the mustache comin' in, Rat?
수염 나오는거 보여?
잡아 뺄수도 있겠어
You can almost cross it out.
천사를 봤어
- I'm in love.
- You are a wuss. Part wimp, part pussy.
넌 쑥맥이야...
소심하고 연약한 면도 있지
쑥맥이라니 무슨 뜻이야?
이 여자애는 내 이상형이라니깐
What do you mean wuss?
This girl is my... exact type.
어디서 봤는데?
- Where'd you see her?
- In my biology class.
생물 시간에
- Did you get her number?
- No.
- 전화번호는 받았어?
- 아니
- Did you get her name?
- No! No! It's too soon.
- 이름은 알아?
- 아니! 너무 이르잖아
너무 이른건 없어
It's never too soon, Rat.
여자랑 얼마나 갈수 있을지는
작업시작 5분안에 끝나는거야
A girl decides how far she's gonna
let you go in the first five minutes.
What am I supposed to do? Go up to
this strange girl in my biology class...
나보고 어떻게 하라고?
생물시간에 모르는
여자에게 가서
and say, "Hello. I'd like you to
take your clothes off and jump on me"?
'안녕, 네 옷을 벗고 나한테
달려 들어 줄래'라고 말하리?
난 그럴걸
I would.
I can see it all now. This is
gonna be just like last summer.
감 잡았어
작년 여름하고 똑같아 지겠구나
사진관 아가씨에게
반해서는
You fell in love
with that girl at the Fotomat.
필름만 40달러어치 샀지만
말 한번 못 붙여 봤잖아
You bought $40 worth of fuckin' film,
and you never even talked to her.
You don't even own a camera!
넌 카메라도 없었잖아!
그럼 어떻게 해?
알면 말해줘
You tell me, Mike.
What should I do?
This is what you do.
이렇게 해봐
생물 시간에
교실에 들어가자 마자
Start from the minute
you walk into biology.
내말은 그냥 들어가란게 아니고
교실을 가로 질러 들어가고
I mean, don't just walk in.
Move across the room.
And you don't talk to her.
말을 거는게 아니라
표정이랑 몸짓을 사용해서
표현을 하는거야
You use your face.
You use your body.
Use everything.
모든걸 사용해
나라면 그렇게 할거야
That's what I do.
내 말은 신호를 보내면...
I mean, I just send out
this vibe...
그 여자는 반응을 보인다는걸
개인적인 경험으로 알아냈지
and I have personally found
that women do respond.
I mean, something happens.
뭔가 일어나지
그건 당연한거지
Naturally something happens.
모든 여자들에게 꼬리를 치면
당연히 뭔가가 일어는 나겠지
You put the vibe out to 30 million
chicks, something is gonna happen.
That's the idea, Rat.
That's the attitude.
바로 그거야
그런 마음가짐이라고
- The attitude?
- Yeah.
마음가짐?
여자가 어떻게 반응을 하던지
신경 안쓸수 있는 마음가짐이 중요해
The attitude dictates
that you don't care whether
she comes, stays, lays or prays.
Whatever happens,
your toes are still tappin'.
어떤 일이 벌어져도 넌
태연해질수 있는거지
Now, when you got that...
then you have the attitude.
네가 그런 경지에 이르면
그런 자세를 가질수 있어
- Good night, Stacy.
- Good night, Mom.
잘 자라, 스테이시
안녕히 주무세요
Just look at that girl with the lights
coming up in her eyes
She's got to be somebody's baby
She must be somebody's baby
예뻐 보인다
- You look beautiful.
- Thanks. So do you.
고마워요
그 쪽도
Where do you feel like going?
어디 갈까?
I don't know.
몰라요
- How 'bout The Point?
- Okay.
경기장에 갈까?
좋아요
All right!
The Point it is.
좋았어!
경기장으로 가자!
She's got to be somebody's baby
She's so fine
She's probably somebody's only light
Gonna shine tonight
Yeah, she's gonna be
somebody's baby tonight
She's gonna be somebody's only light
Gonna shine tonight
Yeah, she's gonna be
somebody's baby tonight
정말 멋진 재킷이예요
That's a really nice jacket.
고마워
Thanks.
Thanks a lot.
따뜻한데
- It's warm.
- Yeah, it is. It's really warm.
네, 정말 따뜻하네요
얼마나 지속 될 지는 모르지만요
I wonder how long it will last.
그래서...
So...
am I gonna get to first base?
1루타는 쳐도 되는거지?
- Are you really 19?
- Yeah, yeah, I am. I'm really 19.
너 정말 19살이야?
네, 진짜 19살 이예요
She's gonna be
somebody's baby tonight
I try to shut my eyes
but I can't get her out of my sight
I know I'm gonna know it
but I gotta get over my fright
I'm just gonna walk up to her
I'm gonna talk to her tonight
Gonna shine tonight
Make her mine tonight?
Yeah
Gonna shine tonight
Make her mine tonight
론이 좋아?
So tell me, do you like Ron?
론은 좋은데 정말 아팠어
I like Ron, but it hurt so bad.
걱정 말고 계속 하면
점점 괜찮아 질거야
Don't worry. Keep doing it.
It gets a lot better. I swear.
그래야지
It better.
Raised on the radio
Just an all
-American boy
I got my favorite toy
I was
raised on the radio
Yeah, I was raised on the radio
Remembering when times were bad
Love is all we need
and love was all we had
- Mom says to clean the pool.
- Why can't you do it?
엄마가 수영장 청소
해놓으라 신다
오빠가 할 순 없었어??
네 친구들이 쓰고
엉망으로 해놓은 거야
Your friends use the pool.
Your friends messed it up.
오빠 친구들도 쓰잖아
- Your friends use the pool too.
- I take out the garbage!
난 쓰레기는 치워!
네 첫경험을 기억하며, 론 존슨
Brad!
오빠!
엄마랑 아빠가
이거 보셨어?
- Brad, have Mom and Dad seen these?
- They're not home yet.
아직 안 오셨어
오빠?
- Brad?
- What?
왜?
만약에 내가 이걸...
What would you say if
I asked you to put these...
오빠차 트렁크에 숨겼다가
버려 달라고 부탁해도 돼?
in the trunk of the Cruising Vessel
and get rid of them?
'누가 론 존슨이냐? '라고 묻겠지
- I'd say, "Who the hell is Ron Johnson?"
- Please.
제발...
정말 고마워
Thank you very much.
- Lisa's great!
- Yeah.
리사는 괜찮은 여자야!
왜 그런 애랑 헤어지려는지
이해를 못하겠어
I don't understand why you want
to break up with a girl like that.
Me and Lisa have been going together
for two years. I love her and all.
나랑 리사는 2년을 사귀었어
사랑은 해
잠자리도 끝내준다고
I mean, she's great in bed.
It's just that...
I'm a single, successful guy.
하지만 그저...
난 성공한 총각이고
올해가 학교에서의 마지막 해고
인생 최고의 해가 될수도 있어!
And this is my last year in school.
This could be the best year of my life!
그저 지금은 나만의
자유를 원할뿐이야, 알아?
I just feel like I need
my freedom now, you know?
좋아, 여기 네 준비물들이야
Okay, here's your preparation stuff.
잘라놓은 토마토는 여기 있고
양배추랑 비밀 소스는 여기 있어
You got your sliced tomatoes,
shredded lettuce, secret sauce.
비밀 소스가 뭔데?
- What's the secret sauce?
- Thousand Island dressing.
샐러드 드레싱
브론코 햄버거 숍의
비밀 소스는 뭐야?
What's the secret sauce
at Bronco Burger?
- 케첩이랑 마요네즈
- 그렇구나
- Ketchup and mayonnaise.
- Gotcha.
주문 들어왔어
Order for you, Bradley.
- Were those flowers really for me?
- Of course!
저 꽃들 정말
날 위한거야?
당연하지!
얼마나 들었는데?
- How much did they cost?
- Don't worry about it.
걱정하지 마
Want to go to The Point tonight?
오늘 밤에 경기장에 갈까?
What's there to do at The Point?
거긴 가서 뭐하게?
What do you mean? We've been
going out together for two years.
무슨 뜻이야? 우린 2년동안
사귀었었어
I don't want to have to use sex
as a tool, Brad.
섹스의 도구로
사용되고 싶지는 않아
도구? 무슨 도구?
우린 2년을 사귀었어!
Tool? Tool for what?
We've been going together for two years!
- I don't want to talk about it here.
- I wanna talk about it!
여기서 말하기 싫어
난 여기서 말하고 싶어!
브래드?
- Brad?
- Lisa!
리사!
Brad!
브래드!
뒤집어야지 안그러면
다 타버려
You gotta flip 'em, or they'll burn.
Great.
'C'
"C."
'D'
"D."
'F'
"F."
'F' 자네도 'F'
"F." "F."
지난 3주간 플랫 개정 헌법에
대하여 공부했습니다
Three weeks we've been talking
about the Platt Amendment.
그렇게 이해가 안가던가요?
What are you people, on dope?
이 사항은 존 플랫 의원에 의해
국회에 소개 되었고
A piece of legislation was introduced
into Congress by Senator John Platt.
1906년에 승인되었습니다
It was passed in 1906.
이 법안의 우리나라
헌법 설립에...
This amendment to our Constitution...
기반을 잡아준...
has a profound impact
upon all of our...
Where is Jeff Spicoli? I saw him earlier
today near the first floor bathrooms.
스피콜리군은 어디 있나요?
1층 화장실 근처에서
아까 봤는데
아직도 학교 안에 있나요?
아는 사람? 네, 데스몬드군?
Is he still on campus?
Anyone? Yes, Desmond?
I saw him by the food machines.
자판기 옆에서 봤어요
- How long ago?
- Right before class.
- 얼마전에 봤나요?
- 수업시작 직전에요
Okay.
Bring him in.
가서 데려 오세요
수업을 빠지는게
무슨 매력이 있단는거죠?
What is this fascination with truancy?
머리속에 무슨 생각들을
하는 겁니까?
What is it that gets inside your heads?
이 학교내의 몇몇 선생님들은
못 본척 넘겨주기도 하지만
There are some teachers in this school
who look the other way at truants.
학생과 선생의
장난질일 뿐이예요
It's a little game
that you both play.
선생들은 학생이 수업빠지는걸
못 본척 해주고 학생들도 마찬가지고
They pretend they don't see you.
You pretend you don't ditch.
나중에 누가 피해를 보죠?
제군들입니다!
Now, who pays the price later?
You!
이거 뭐야?
내 생일파티 안하잖아!
Wait a minute.
There's no birthday party for me here!
Hola, Mr. Hand.
안녕하세요, 선생님
What's the reason for your truancy?
수업을 빠진
이유가 뭡니까?
Just couldn't make it on time.
제 시간에
못 온것 뿐이예요
You mean,
you couldn't or you wouldn't?
못 온건가요 아님
안 온건가요?
음식들이 너무 많이
보였었어요
It was like a full crowd scene
at the food lines.
음식은 개인적인 시간에
먹도록 해요
Food will be eaten on your time.
왜 계속해서 이 수업에
늦게 오는건가요, 스피콜리군?
Why are you continuously late
for this class, Mr. Spicoli?
Why do you shamelessly waste
my time like this?
왜 이렇게 부끄럽게 제 시간을
허비 시키는 거죠?
- I don't know.
-
모르겠어요
맘에 드는군요
I like that.
"I don't know."
That's nice!
모르겠어요
좋군요!
"Mr. Hand,
will I pass this class?"
선생님, 제가 이 반에서
낙제 하지 않을까요?
"Gee, Mr. Spicoli,
I don't know!"
이런, 스피콜리군
나도 잘 모르겠어요!
좋아요, 맘에 들어요
내가 어떻게 할지 알아요?
That's nice. I really like that.
You know what I'm gonna do?
이 말을 칠판에 계속 적어 둘테니
보면서 즐기도록 해요
I'm going to leave your words on this
board for all my classes to enjoy.
물론 이 반을 통과를
시켜주죠, 스피콜리군!
Giving you full credit,
of course, Mr. Spicoli!
All right.
좋죠
Sleigh bells ring
are you listening
- Mommy!
- In the lane
엄마!
이런
- Oh, no!
- Snow is glistening
A beautiful sight
We're happy tonight
Walking in a winter wonderland
얼마나 더 기다려야 해?
How fucking long
do I have to wait?
크리스마스인데 정말 싫다
Christmas sucks.
I hate it.
사람들이 늘 소릴 질러도
휴일에도 일하는데 익숙해 져야 돼
You gotta get used to working holidays.
People are always screaming.
I have to quit this job.
I'm gonna get so fat...
나 일 관둘거야
여기 있다간 살이 너무 쪄서
아무도 날 안데려 갈거야
- no one's gonna want to take me out.
- Ron hasn't called, huh?
론한테 전화 안왔구나?
- Not since November.
- What does it matter?
He's a stereo salesman.
11월 이후엔 한번도...
도대체 왜 그래?
걘 겨우 전파상 세일즈맨이야
어쩌려고? 론이랑 결혼해서
애 낳고 살래?
What'd you wanna do, marry him?
Have kids with him?
나중에 머리 다 빠진
아저씨랑 살고 싶어?
Have this guy come home
50 years old and bald?
미래도 없어 보이는 사람이랑?
정신차려, 스테이시
And have that little Pacific Stereo
sign on? Come on, Stace.
Hey, it's his loss.
그 사람이 복을
차 버린거야
블루 오이스터 컬트
티켓 있어요?
Got any Blue Oyster Cult?
No, I don't have any
Blue Oyster Cult.
아니, 없어
지난 번에 34장이나 손해 봤는데
어디 있었냐?
I ate 34 pairs last time.
Where were you?
하마터면 편의점에서
일할뻔 했잖아, 알어?
I was that close to working
at 7-Eleven, you know.
What?
뭐?
- 좋아, 한판 할까?
- 당근이지
- All right! Play me?
- Totally.
동전 있어?
You got quarters?
대지, 바람, 불의 티켓이
언제 들어오냐?
When are those Earth, Wind and Fire
tickets comin' in?
대지, 바람, 불?
아직 들은바 없는데
Earth, Wind and Fire?
Geez, I haven't heard anything.
The minute I do,
I'll let you know.
콘서트 소식 들으면
바로 알려줄게
I'm plannin' on taking
my little brother over here.
저기 있는 내 동생을
데려갈 계획이야
Is that your little brother?
He's a good-lookin' kid.
저게 네 동생이야?
잘 생겼네
알았어, 찰스 제퍼슨이랑...
Great.
Charles Jefferson...
for Earth, Wind and Fire
and little brother.
동생이 대지, 바람, 불의
티켓을 원함
I'll let you know when
they come around, okay?
여기서 콘서트 하면
바로 알려줄게
와! 저 형 이 동네 살았어요?
경기날만 날아오는줄 알았어요
Wow! Does he really live here?
I thought he just flew in for games.
티켓을 어디로 구하러
와야하는질 잘 알잖아
Shit! He knows where to come
when he wants some tickets.
저리가
내 장사에 방해 되잖아
Go on. Get outta here.
You're messing up my business.
Come on, Rat.
Let's go get you a woman.
마크, 네 여자나
보러 가자
Wow.
You ready for
your moment of truth?
운명의 시간
준비됐어?
마이크, 오늘 아침에
여드름이 하나 생겼걸랑...
Damone, I noticed I was starting
to get a pimple this morning...
Rat, the shyness routine
is really starting to aggravate me.
네 그 쑥맥 정신에 이젠
짜증나기 시작한다
도대체 어떤 여자길래 그래?
그저 피자가게 종업원이라고
I mean, who is she, anyway?
She's a waitress in a pizza parlor.
Look at her. Look at you.
A member of the Honor Roll.
쟬 봐봐, 그리고 넣 봐
넌 모범생 킹카에
극장 부 지점장의
비서실장이라고
Assistant to the assistant manager
of the movie theater.
만약 저 여자가
네 가치를 모른다면
Rat, if this girl
can't smell your qualifications,
then who needs her, right?
저 여자 손해지 않아?
- 맞아
- 좋아, 기분 어때?
- Right.
- All right. How do you feel?
- 좋아
- 정말? 좋았어
- I feel good.
- Do ya? All right.
이제 바보짓은 그만하고
가서 꼬셔봐
Now stop fucking around
and go get her.
마크, 그 웃옷은 벗어야지
Hey, Rat, you gotta ace that jacket.
- Yeah?
- Yeah. All right, that's cool.
좋아, 괜찮아 보이네
You look good. All right?
Go get her.
알았어? 가 봐
1달러 10센트고
거스름돈은 5센트요
$1.10, and you get five cents back.
Thanks.
고마워요
- Hi! Don't I know you
from biology class?
- Yeah!
우리 같은 생물시간
듣지 않니?
- What can I do for you?
- I had a couple of questions.
I was curious.
뭐 줄까?
질문이 두개 있는데...
What do you do with the
jackets people leave here?
사람들이 놓고간 재킷들을
어떻게 처리해?
- We keep 'em.
- You keep 'em?
보관 해 두지
보관해?
찾으러 올 경우를 대비하지
원하면 한번 찾아봐
In case they come back.
You can look through it if you want.
괜찮아, 그걸 전부 보려면
너무 오래 걸릴것 같아
No, that's cool. It would take
too long to look through all that.
I'll pick up a new one.
새 걸 하나 살래
What was your other question?
또 다른 질문은 뭐야?
Oh, my other question is...
내 다른 질문은...
가끔 연락하게
네 전화번호 줄래?
can I have your phone number
so I can ask you out sometime?
- Do you have a pen?
This one's out of ink.
- Yeah.
펜 있어?
이건 잉크가 없어서
만나서 반가웠어, 스테이시
난 마크 래트너야
Stacy. Nice to meet you, Stacy.
My name is Mark Ratner.
이제 가야 해
I've gotta go.
아가씨, 한번 하자
리사, 할 말이 있어
Lisa, I have something to tell you.
이제 우린 고(高)3 이잖아
Look, I'm a senior now.
난 성공한 싱글이고
I'm a single, successful guy.
And I've got to be fair to myself.
나 자신에게 충실해 줘야 해
난 자유가 필요한 것 같아
Lisa... I think I need my freedom.
그러지 마
Oh, don't do that.
제발, 이러지 마
- Please, please don't do that.
- Brad!
2번 창구 대신 잠깐만 봐줄래?
- Can you cover me on register two?
- Okay.
알았어
- May I help you?
- Ah, yes.
- 도와 드려요?
- 그래
아침치곤 너무 엉망이야
내 돈을 돌려 줘
This is not the best breakfast
I ever ate and...
- I'd like my money back.
- Okay. I believe
you have to fill out a form.
네, 서류를 꾸며주셔야
하는걸로 아는데...
No. I'd like my money back now.
아니, 난 당장 환불을 바래
죄송하지만 그렇게는 안돼고
서류를 꾸며주셔야 해요
I'm sorry. It doesn't work that way.
I have to fill out a form.
Well, you ate most of it
already so...
이미 거의 다 드셨고...
저기 표지 보이나?
See that sign?
It says "100% guaranteed."
'만족'이란 단어의 뜻 몰라?
여기서 그런거 안가르치나?
You know what the meaning
of guarantee is?
Did they teach you that here?
선생님, 잠깐만 시간을
주신다면...
Sir, if you'd just wait a minute.
이봐, 금전통 안에
잔말말고 손을 넣고
Look. Just put your little hand
in the cash register...
and give me my $2.75 back,
please, Brad.
내 2달러 75센트를 돌려줘
브래드
Sir, if you'd just give me a minute.
I'll find the forms.
I'll take care of everything.
잠깐만 시간을 주시면 서류를 찾아
모든걸 해결해 드리겠습니다
난 그 잠깐도 시간이 없어
이미 날 늦게 만들었어
I don't have a minute.
You've made me late enough.
불만족함을 참는데도
이젠 지쳤어
I am so tired of dealing
with incompetence.
100% 만족 보장이라잖아
이 멍청한 자식아!
It says 100% guaranteed,
you moron!
Mister, if you don't shut up,
I'm gonna kick 100% of your ass.
아저씨, 당장 닥치지 않으면
Ah, is there a problem here?
Can I help you, sir?
문제가 있나?
도와 드릴까요, 선생님?
You bet you have a problem.
Your employee used profanity
and threatened me with violence.
정말 문제가 많소
자네 부하직원이 욕설과
폭력으로 날 협박했소
매일 여기서 식사를 하고 서비스가
좋았는데, 기가 막히군요
I'm surprised. I eat here all the time
and usually have good service.
내가 바란건 오직 여기 덜 구워진
아침 식사에 대한 환불이었는데
All I wanted was my money back on this
breakfast. It was a little under-cooked.
이 자가 폭력을 쓰며 날 협박했어요
이곳 지점장을 불러서...
And he threatens me with violence.
I'm gonna call your super...
I can take care of it.
제가 도와드리죠
해밀튼군, 손님께 협박을 하거나
욕설을 사용했나?
Mr. Hamilton, did you threaten this
customer or use profanity in any way?
Uh... he insulted me first.
He called me a moron, Dennis.
먼저 욕을 했어요
저보고 멍청한 놈이라고 했어요
대답만 해! 손님께 협박을 하거나
욕설을 사용했나?
Answer me! Did you threaten
this customer or use profanity?
- Yes.
- You're fired.
- 네
- 자넨 해고야
I'm very sorry, sir.
I'll refund your money right now.
대단히 죄송합니다, 손님
당장 돈은 환불 해드리겠습니다
I hope you won't hold this against us.
감정은 없으셨길 바랍니다
요즘 젊은것들은
버릇이 없어 문제예요
You know how these young kids are
these days.
여기 있습니다
다른것으로 드시겠습니까?
Here we are.
Perhaps another breakfast?
오줌싸다 빠져 죽었냐, 자식아!
I hope you had
a hell of a piss, Arnold!
1946년 이후 이 해변을
강타한 최대의 파도를 이긴
The world's finest
surfers showed up today to do battle...
with what's turned out to be the biggest
waves to hit this coast since 1946.
세계 최고의 서퍼가
탄생 했습니다
안녕하세요, 스투 나한입니다
그 주인공인 제프 스피콜리를
Hello. I'm Stu Nahan,
and I'd like you to meet this young man.
His name, Jeff Spicoli.
Jeff, congratulations.
소개 합니다
축하해요, 제프군
Things looked rough out there today.
오늘 상황이 많이
힘들어 보이던데요...
정말 커다란 파도랑
전쟁을 벌였지만
I'll tell you, Stu,
I did battle with some humongous waves.
ABC방송국 기자에게 말했듯이
'위험해도 이건 제 임무죠'
Just like I told the guy on ABC,
"Danger is my business."
많은 사람들이 마크 데이비스나
봅 제랄드가
A lot of people
expected Mark "Cutback" Davis,
or Bob "Jungle Vet" Gerard...
올해 우승을 차지할거라고
예상을 했었죠
- would take the honors this year.
- Those guys are fags!
그 사람들은 엉터리예요!
좋습니다
Let me ask you. When you get out there,
do you ever fear for your life?
하나만 묻죠, 바다에 나갔을때
목숨을 잃을까 겁나지 않았었나요?
서핑은 스포츠도 아니고
취미도 아닌 인생 그 자체예요
Stu, surfing's not a sport.
It's a way of life. It's no hobby.
그렇게 생각을 하고 나가면
파도가...
It's a way of looking at that wave
and saying, "Hey, bud, let's party!"
'이봐, 친구, 파티를 시작하자고!'
라고 말하죠
Where'd you get this jacket?
그 양복 어디서 났어요?
From the network. Let me ask you,
what's next for Jeff Spicoli?
방송국에서 받았어요
다음 계획은 뭔가요?
일단 호주에서 대회를 치룬 후
하와이 대회를 나갈 겁니다
Headed over to the Australian
and then the Hawaiian Internationals.
그 다음엔 런던으로 날아가서
롤링 스톤즈랑 연주 같이 해야죠
Then me and Mick are gonna wing on over
to London and jam with the Stones.
You guys are invited too.
너희들도 초대할게 가자
Jeff! Jeff!
Jeff, Dad says you have to get up.
- 아빠가 형 이제 일어나래
- 냅둬
- Leave me alone.
- Dad says you're gonna be late again,
you butthole!
빨리 안 일어나면 또 늦는대
이 잠꾸러기야!
- Leave me alone!
- Dad says you're gonna be late again,
you booger!
냅두라니깐!
아빠가 빨리 안 일어나면 또
늦는대, 이 밥통아!
Dad, Jeff threw his snorkel at me!
아빠, 형이 잠수장비를 나한테
던졌어요!
We just want to say that
we're not Spirit Bunnies anymore.
우린 더 이상 남자들의 노리개가
아니라는걸 말하고 싶었어
We always hated that name.
It bugged the heck out of Dina and me.
그 말이 젤 듣기 싫지
정말 짜증 나는 단어였어
- 정말 저질적인 말이야!
- 정말 그래!
- It's just such a put-down!
- Really!
We know you've got a lot of spirit,
everybody, right?
모두 학교 사랑하는 마음이
엄청난거 맞지?
다음주에 링컨 고등학교를
묵사발을 만들어 줄거야!
And we're gonna destroy Lincoln
next week! All right!
여기 앞에 나와서 뻔히 알면서도
사람들이 놀릴 짓을 하려면
You know, it takes a lot
of courage to get up here...
and do something that
you know people will make fun of.
정말 많은
용기가 필요해
- Yeah.
- Man...
젠장...
그 자식들이랑 두번 다시
말도 안 할거야
I'm never gonna talk
to those guys again.
아놀드랑 데이브 취직을
시켜준건 나였어
I'm the one who got Arnold and Dave
their jobs there in the first place.
가서 사과만 하면
다시 일 시켜 줄거야
If you'd apologize to Dennis,
I'm sure he'd take you back.
됐다고 봐!
내가 뭘 잘못해서 사과를 해!
Fuck Dennis Taylor!
I'm not gonna apologize to that wimp.
그저 우리가 아직도
사귀고 있어서 다행이야
I'm just glad
we're still together...
많은 일이 벌어졌고
올해 네가 정말 옆에 있어주길 바래
because a lot's happened,
and I really need you this year.
브래드, 어떻게 이 말을 해야 하나
참 많이 망설였었걸랑...
Look, Brad, I've been trying
to think of a way to tell you this.
졸업도 얼마 안 남았어
We're almost out of school.
It's our last year.
올해가 마지막이잖아
우리 스스로에게 자유가
필요할거라고 생각해
And I think we owe it
to ourselves to be free,
to go out with other people.
다른 사람들도
사귀어 봐야지
물론 계속 친구론 남을거야
I still want to be friends.
What do I say to her
once we get in the car?
차에 탄 다음에
무슨 말을 해야 해?
걱정마, 내 5가지
특수 연예 비법이면 돼
No problem, Rat. What you need
is my special five-point plan.
장난 하지 마
나 정말 도움이 필요해
Come on, Damone,
I need real help.
무슨 뜻이야?
내 이 비법을 얻으려고
What'd you mean?
Men have died...
trying to obtain this
valuable information.
얼마나 많은 사람들이
죽어간지 알아?
- But I'll give it to you for free.
- What's your five-point plan?
하지만 넌 공짜로 알려주지
네 5가지 비법이 뭔데?
좋아, 잘 들어
All right.
Now, pay attention.
첫째로 네가 얼마나 좋아하는지를
여자가 모르게 해
First of all, you never let on
how much you like a girl.
Oh, Debbie... hi.
데비구나...
안녕...
Two.
You always call the shots.
둘째, 항상 네가 먼저 이끌어
키스하자, 후회하지 않을거야
Kiss me, you won't regret it.
셋째, 어디 있던지 간에 그 곳을
있고 싶은 장소로 만들어 줘
Three. Act like wherever you are,
that's the place to be.
여기 괜찮지 않니?
Isn't this great?
Four.
넷째
음식을 주문할 땐 여자가 뭘
원하는질 알아내고 시켜
When ordering food, find out what she
wants, then order for the both of you.
It's a classy move.
아주 멋진 방법이지
The lady will have
the linguine in a white clam sauce,
여자들은 대부분
소스를 얹은 파스타와
얼음없는 콜라를 같이 시키지
and a coke with no ice.
And five.
그리고 다섯번째
이게 가장 중요한거야
Now, this is most important, Rat.
언제고 아주 섬세한 작업을
들어가게 되면...
When it comes down to makin' out,
whenever possible,
가능한한 시간이 긴
음악을 미리 틀어놔
put on side one
of Led Zeppelin IV.
차 좋은데
- This is a nice car.
- Yeah. It's my sister's.
응, 우리 누나 차야
Yeah?
혹시 조지선생님의
영어반에 있지 않니?
Do you have Mrs. George
for English?
응, 그 선생님 좋더라
- Yeah. She's pretty good.
- Yeah, she is pretty good.
응, 괜찮은 분이시지
정했니?
- Have you decided?
- Um, yeah.
난 독일 소시지 먹을래
I'll have the knockwurst.
Excellent.
좋아
You work at Cinema Four, right?
너 극장에서 일하지?
That must be great.
You get to see all those free movies.
좋겠다...
영화는 다 공짜로 보잖아
You get free popcorn.
팝콘도 다 공짜일테고
괜찮아?
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
응
잠깐만 실례 좀
해도 괜찮을까?
Would you mind if I excuse
myself for a moment?
Oh, no, go ahead.
그래
주문 하시겠어요?
Are you ready to order here?
얘는 독일 소시지를 주세요
She will have the knockwurst.
And you?
그리고요?
저도 같은걸로 주세요
- I'll have the same.
- Anything to drink?
마실것은요?
- Coke.
- Two Cokes.
- 콜라요
- 콜라 두 잔이요
Okay.
Thank you.
고맙습니다
- 금방 올게
- 알았어
- I'll be right back.
- Okay.
- Hello?
- Mike, it's Mark.
- 여보세요?
- 마이크, 나 마크야
- What happened to your date?
- It's happening right now.
Everything's fine except...
데이트는 잘하고 있어?
한가지만 빼곤
다 잘 풀려나가는 중인데...
I left my wallet at home.
집에 지갑을 두고 왔어
Why don't you go home and get it?
그럼 집에 가서 가져 가
No, I can't! I'm here.
The food's coming and everything.
지금 그렇게를 못해!
조금 있으면 음식이 나올거야
나 좀 도와줘
Look, would you do me a favor?
엄마 차를 빌려서
우리집으로 가서
Just borrow your mom's car, drive to my
house, get my wallet and bring it here.
내 지갑 가지고
이리 와줘
Hello? Mike?
여보세요?
마이크?
Mike?
이런, 나 지금 좀 바빠
Geez, I'm really kinda busy, Rat.
Just do me this one favor.
이번 한번만 도와주라
평생동안 앞으로는 어떤 부탁도
하지 않을 테니 제발...
I swear I won't ask you for anything
again in this lifetime or any other.
이번만 좀 도와줘
- But just please do this for me.
- You owe me for this one.
나중에 너 이거 갚아
Okay, thanks.
Thanks a lot. Thanks.
알았어, 고마워
정말 고마워
- Beaver, are you all right?
- What happened?
비버, 너 괜찮아?
뭐야?
Are you sure there's nothing else
I can bring you?
더 필요한거 정말로
없어요?
Do you want another Coke?
콜라 더 마실래?
Um... okay.
그래
Two more Cokes.
콜라 두잔 더요
콜라 두잔 더
- Hey, Mark, is that you?
- Yeah, hi.
- 마크, 너 맞아?
- 응, 안녕
- 여긴 왠일이야?
- 독일 파스타 먹으러 왔지
- You come here?
- Yeah. I come for the strudel.
It's great.
지난번에 네 지갑을 찾았는데
돌려줄까?
Hey, listen, I found your wallet
the other day. You want it back?
와! 그래
이걸 얼마나 찾았던지...
Oh, wow! Yeah.
I was looking for this.
마이크, 스테이시 모르지?
Oh, Mike,
you don't know Stacy Hamilton.
스테이시, 이쪽은 마이크야
- Stacy, this is Mike Damone.
- Hi.
- Nice to meet you.
만나서 반갑다
See you later.
나중에 보자
Right. Gotta be goin'.
See you later.
그래, 이제 가야지
나중에 보자
You wanna go?
갈까?
Um... yeah.
그래
오늘 정말 즐거웠어
- I had a really nice time tonight.
- Me too.
나도
누가 네 차를 부수고
카세트를 훔쳐가서 정말 유감이야
I'm real sorry someone broke in
and stole your tape deck.
그런 좋은 동네에서 그런 일이
벌어질줄은 생각도 못했어
I never thought it would've happened
at such a fancy place.
알아
잠깐 들어왔다 갈래?
I know.
You want to come in for a sec?
- 그래, 물론
- 좋아
- Okay, sure.
- Good.
오빠는 어디갔어?
- Where's your brother?
- He's out tonight with some friends.
친구들이랑 나갔어
- 마실것 가져다 줄까?
- 아니, 괜찮아
- Can I get you something to drink?
- No, that's... that's okay.
Oh. Well,
would you mind if I change?
나 옷 좀 갈아 입어도 괜찮겠지?
No.
그래
그럼 이것 좀 풀어줄래?
항상 걸려 안 움직여
Okay. Could you get this for me?
It always sticks.
고마워
Thanks.
Where are your parents?
부모님은 어디 가셨어?
My parents are out of town
for the weekend.
주말동안 여행 가셨어
Brad and I are watching the house.
오빠랑 내가 집 지키는 중이야
- This is a really nice picture of you.
- Thanks.
- 사진 정말 예쁘게 나왔다
- 고마워
You can come in my room
if you want.
내 방에 들어와
뭐 하고 싶어?
So, what do you want to do?
글쎄...
I don't know.
Um, you want to look
at a photo album?
내 사진첩 볼래?
어릴때부터 사진을
다 가지고 있어
I keep a lot of pictures
from when I grew up and stuff.
- 너무 바보같은가?
- 아니, 사진 보자
- It's kinda stupid, huh?
- Sure! Yeah.
정말? 좋아
Yeah? Great.
Photographs.
사진들
This is the one that Brad took.
이건 오빠가 찍은 사진이야
이건 거울속에 비친
모습같은 거야
It's like double-image type thing,
you know. It's like a mirror.
This is me being stupid.
이건 내가 바보짓 하는 거고
And this is my dog Gypsy,
and my cat Tullio.
이건 키우던 개 집시랑
고양이 툴리오인데
- They're dead now.
- Remember him? Mr. Degan?
지금은 죽었어
누군지 기억나? 디건 선생님?
You had Degan?
디건 선생님 반이었어?
- He always wore the same suit!
- The same suit!
맨날 똑같은 옷만 입잖아!
그 옷이 500개는 넘나봐
- He must've had 500 of those suits.
- He was terrible!
정말 끔찍했지!
아마 단벌신사였을거야
No, I think it was one.
So you go out there
and you get one too
Love rules
Ohh, love rules
Yeah, love rules
갑자기 생각이 났는데
- You know, I just thought of something.
- What?
차에 관해서는 우리 누나는
장난이 아니게 민감해
My sister is crazy
when it comes to her car.
- 11시까지 돌려줘야 하거든
- 전화 할래?
- It's gotta be back by 11:00.
- Want to call her?
No. Look, l...
She gets crazy.
아니, 그러니깐...
정말 화내
누난 차를 아기처럼 아껴
Her car is her baby.
- 가야겠어
- 그럴래?
- I better be going.
- Really?
전화 할게
아니 학교에서 보자
I'll call you.
Well, I'll see you in class. Okay?
알았지?
Bye.
잘있어
Love rules
- Mark Ratner doesn't like me.
- Mark Ratner doesn't like you?
You're crazy!
마크가 날 안 좋아해
말이 돼?
아니 정말로 나한테 아예
관심이 없는걸 비췄어
No, he shows absolutely
no interest in me.
마크는 네가 먼저 작업을
들어가야 하는 스타일이야
Mark Ratner is definitely somebody
you'd have to make the first move with.
린다, 그렇게 했지, 내가 먼저
온갖 유혹을 했지만
Linda, I did. I made the first move,
I made the second move.
나만 완전 바보 됐다니깐
I made a complete jerk out of myself,
is what I did.
마크 같은 애는 신경 꺼!
What do you care about
Mark Ratner for?
그저 16살짜리
극장 문지기일 뿐이야
He's a 16-year-old usher
in the movie theater.
넌 더 나이 많은
남자랑 사귀어 봤고
You have dated older guys. You work
at the best food stand in the mall.
백화점 최고 음식점에서
일하고 있고
넌 나랑 가장 친한 친구야
And you are a close
personal friend of mine.
응, 하지만 마크가 정말로
좋아지기 시작했어
Yeah. But I was really
beginning to like him.
그래? 그게 사실이면
너 빨리 다른 사람을 만나야 겠다
Yeah? If that's true,
you better find somebody else fast.
이번 플레이 보이지 봤어?
- Seen the new Playboy?
- Good?
괜찮아?
쭉쭉빵빵이야!
- Bo Derek's tits!
- All right!
좋았어!
I like sex.
난 섹스가 좋아
운전 못하는 사람들은
면허증을 뺏어야 한다니깐
People on ludes
should not drive.
이거 우리 형 차야!
Hey, this is my brother's car!
- 형 여행 갔다며
- 그렇지
- You said he was outta town.
- And he is.
알았어, 그럼 걱정할게 없잖아
All right.
Then don't hassle it.
Are you crazy, Spicoli?
That light was red!
미쳤어?
빨간불이었어!
- It was yellow a minute ago.
- You're gonna scratch my brother's car.
그 전에 노란불이었어
이러다 우리 형차에
흠집 내겠어
아니, 그럴 일 없어
No, I'm not.
운전은 내가 하니깐
넌 길이나 잘 봐
Look, I'm driving.
You navigate.
파티를 어디서 하는거야?
Where is this party?
여기서 우회전해
여기, 여기야!
Make a right, right here.
Here! Here! Here!
형이 우릴 둘 다 죽일거야!
우린 둘 다 죽었어!
My brother's gonna kill us!
He's gonna kill us!
He's gonna kill you. He's gonna kill me.
형도 죽일거고
나도 죽이고 둘 다 죽일거야!
Hey, man, just be glad
I had fast reflexes.
야, 내가 반사작용이
빨랐던걸 고맙게 생각해
- My brother's gonna shit!
- Make up your mind, dude.
우리 형이 우릴 팰거야!
도대체 어떤거야?
우릴 팰거야 아님 죽일거야?
Is he gonna shit,
or is he gonna kill us?
우릴 죽을때까지
팰거야
First he's gonna shit,
then he's gonna kill us.
침착해, 알았어?
울 아버지가 TV 수리공이야
Relax, all right?
My old man is a television repairman.
He's got this ultimate set of tools.
I can fix it!
모든 장비가 다 있으니
내가 고칠수 있어
그걸로 차는 수리 못해!
You can't fix this car, Spicoli!
고칠수 있어
- I can fix it.
- Ha.